[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "type": "MCQ",
    "question": "What does this code do",
    "options": ["a", "b", "c"],
    "answer": "a",
    "marks": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "type": "Structured",
    "question": "Describe this code.",
    "answer": "this is a test",
    "marks": 5,
    "students": [
      {
        "name": "bob",
        "marks": 2
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "type": "Code",
    "question": "What does this code do",
    "answer": "hello world",
    "marks": 10
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "type": "MCQ",
    "question": "What does this code do",
    "options": ["a", "b", "c"],
    "answer": "a",
    "marks": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "type": "Structured",
    "question": "Describe this code.",
    "answer": "this is a test",
    "marks": 5,
    "students": [
      {
        "name": "bob",
        "marks": 2
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "type": "Code",
    "question": "What does this code do",
    "answer": "hello world",
    "marks": 10
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "type": "MCQ",
    "question": "What does this code do",
    "options": ["a", "b", "c"],
    "answer": "a",
    "marks": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "type": "Structured",
    "question": "Describe this code.",
    "answer": "this is a test",
    "marks": 5,
    "students": [
      {
        "name": "bob",
        "marks": 2
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "type": "Code",
    "question": "What does this code do",
    "answer": "hello world",
    "marks": 10
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "type": "MCQ",
    "question": "What does this code do",
    "options": ["a", "b", "c"],
    "answer": "a",
    "marks": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "type": "Structured",
    "question": "Describe this code.",
    "answer": "this is a test",
    "marks": 5,
    "students": [
      {
        "name": "bob",
        "marks": 2
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "type": "Code",
    "question": "What does this code do",
    "answer": "hello world",
    "marks": 10
  }
]
